healthbase.com 2014-04-24

# 

Healthbase Online Inc, a Delaware state company with its principal office in the Massachusetts state which owns and operates the www.healthbase.com web site cares about the privacy of each user that comes to its site.  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Healthbase at legal.hb@healthbase.com. If you have technical difficulty using our Web site, please contact our Webmaster at the email address in our web site.   
Healthbase recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information we collect from our on-line users. We are committed to respecting the privacy of anyone coming to the Healthbase site. We design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind.   
This Privacy Policy describes how Healthbase collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. It also describes the choices available to you regarding Healthbase's use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or delete it. 

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing.  
Unless you choose to provide personally identifying information about you when you visit Healthbase, we don't collect such information. Healthbase will never ask your password or social security number by phone, email or online anytime. We do not store any credit card information in our system.   
If you become a Healthbase member we will require certain additional information from you in order to establish your account, to identify your interest in services for health care, travel and related activities, to facilitate communication of relevant information about you to these service providers according to your instructions, and to maintain your records. If you have signed up for our Newsletter, a special offer service from us and our partners, you will be contacted by email regarding special offers, new products, and newsletters.  
We gather certain information like your ip address and which sections of our site you visit at our website in order to evaluate, deliver, and improve our service to you. This information allows us to improve the content of our site, service offerings, as well as to customize our site to meet your needs better.   
For marketing, promotional, and business purposes, we may also use aggregated information, which does not identify you personally. Our member lists, your personal identifying information, or transaction data will not be sold to any other person or entity in the ordinary courses of our business. But we reserve the right to transfer such information in connection with a change in ownership of Healthbase or its assets. We also may disclose information as described below under the "Security" heading. 

Your Access to and Control Over Information.  
You may contact us at the address given in our website to update, change or delete your personal information at any time. In addition, you can update your personal information directly online by logging on to our secured site at https://www.healthbase.com. If you have any concerns regarding this, please contact us at legal.hb@healthbase.com or using the phone number or email at our website.   
Cookies.   
We make limited use of "cookies," which are small sets of text information stored onto your computer in connection with your use of our website. We use cookies to store temporary individual user information concerning your use of this site and your user identification. We do not use cookies to collect or store personally identifiable information. Our site can't read other data on your hard drive or read cookies created by other sites. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Other Web Sites.   
Our site includes links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Healthbase. If you submit your information to any of those sites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any web site you visit. If you use a link from Healthbase's site to another site, or if you arrived at Healthbase through a link from another site, it is also possible that these other sites may place a cookie or other identifier on your computer. We do not control and are not responsible for the use of cookies, policies, practices or content of anyone except Healthbase. 

Security.   
We take precautions to protect your information. Wherever we collect sensitive information such as your personal data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption for transmitting personal information. You can verify this by looking for a "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page, or by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser. Just like we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job, for example, customer service are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers n which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. We routinely monitor and upgrade our security systems to ensure that we use the best security technology available.   
Listed below are some of the security procedures that Healthbase uses to protect your privacy:   
Requires both a personal username and a password in order for users to access their personal information.   
Utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption in transmitting personal information to our servers. In order to take advantage of encryption technology, you must have an Internet browser which supports 128-bit encryption.   
Requires all Healthbase employees to abide by our Privacy Policy.   
Limits access to personal information to authorized users only.   
Healthbase enables you to have full control over who has access to your personal information.   
We use efforts consistent with sound industry practice, such as firewalls and SSL encryption, to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifying information. Given the nature of the Internet, we cannot ensure complete security and we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of any person or entity other than Healthbase. In addition, Healthbase cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, we obey court orders, and we honor subpoenas and other legal process. Your personal identifying information may be disclosed if we are compelled by law or legal process to disclose it. We may also disclose such information if we determine in our sole discretion that disclosure would be useful in connection with investigating possible non-compliance either with the law or with any Healthbase policy including this Privacy Policy. Although we take precautions against security breaches, hackers pose a threat to any Internet user, and the legal and regulatory status of matters on the Internet is uncertain both in the United States and abroad. For these reasons, we cannot guarantee that all of your private communications and other personal identifying information will never be disclosed in ways you do not expect or which are not described in this Privacy Policy. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to see that your information is treated in compliance with this Privacy Policy. 

Changes in Healthbase Policy and Website Maintenance.  
As our business grows or changes, and as technology and Internet use and practices change, Healthbase may from time to time change its policies, potentially including this Privacy Policy. If any such changes are made, they will be posted on this website. Therefore we encourage you to review our Privacy Policy and other policies posted on this site for potential changes when you return to the site for future visits or to transact business.   
Healthbase accepts no responsibility for the loss or additional expense caused to the users by any acts of God, dangers, incidental to the sea, fire, breakdown, or equipment, adverse weather, acts of government, or other authorities, wars, whether declared or not, hostilities, civil disturbances, political instability or unrest, strikes, labor disputes, riots, thefts, pilferage, epidemics, quarantine, customs regulations, delays, changes in itinerary or schedules, by any other cause, condition or event whatsoever beyond the control of Healthbase.   
We at Healthbase are sincerely committed to a safe and secure web experience for our visitors. If, after reading all this, you have concerns or questions, contact us at legal.hb@healthbase.com.
